>> Jem Young: 所以让我们把它放下，让我们先从标题开始。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So let's break it down,
let's start with the headers.
>> Jem Young: 什么是标题?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: What is a header?
或者您对标题是什么以及它的内容是什么 ?
Or what is your take on what
a header is and what it does?
>> 扬声器 2: 元数据 [INAUDIBLE] 请求。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Metadata
[INAUDIBLE] the request.
>> Jem Young: 对不起?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Sorry?
>> 扬声器 2: 提供一些元数据。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Give some metadata.
>> Jem Young: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah.
>> 扬声器 2: [INAUDIBLE] 请求或响应。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE] request or
the response.
>> Jem Young: 是的，或者我们说的信息包是由数据组成的，然后是元数据?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, or we said packets
are made up of data and then metadata?
元数据的一部分是标题，标题是真实的，
Part of that meta data is the header,
and the header is something really,
很有趣的是我们在某个时候都在用
really interesting that we all
probably use at some point but
我们不考虑它在做什么
we don't think about what it's doing.
这个元数据的伟大之处在于它可以告诉很多人
And the great thing about this metadata
is it can tell a lot about like where
这一要求不仅是 IP的问题。
the request has come
from besides just the IP.
它说明它有什么样的编码，它有什么样的内容，
It tells what kind of encoding it has,
what kind of content it has,
它其实有很多我们可以收拾和卸载的信息
it actually has so much information
that we can pack and unload.
并且您可以了解该请求是如何形成的，以及它来自何处，以及
And you can understand how that request
is formed and where it came from, and
我们可以沿着这条路连接信息
we can attach information along the path.
实际上，我可以附加页眉或者 Nginx 将阅读的内容，仅适用于 Nginx 。
In fact, I can attach headers or something
that Nginx will read, just for Nginx, it
把它带出去然后就到快车去看他自己的头，
strips it out and then it goes to Express,
then Express will read his own headers,
也许会把这些数据传递出去但它会引出另一个标题
maybe pass that data along something
else but it strips out another header.
因此，我们可以在添加信息或转移信息的过程中，
So along the way we can add information or
subtract information,
这才是最棒的
that's what headers are really good for.
你有问题吗
Do you have a question?
> > 众议长 3: 是的，我觉得就像在信封外面写的一样，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah, I think that like the
writing on the outside of the envelope,
因为包或内容，然后头是您可以
because the packets or the content, and
then the headers are the part that you can
在不需要查看内容的情况下进行检查。
inspect without having
to look at the contents.
>> Jem Young: 没错，我再次喜欢这个信封的比喻，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly, and
I love the envelope metaphor, again,
是谁创造的
who created that?
我以为是我，不， [洛杉矶 ]
I thought it was me, no,
[LAUGH] it's exactly that,
所有关于目的地的信息都是从哪里来的
it's all this information about where
a destination is going, where it's from,
它使用什么样的编码，它接受什么样的编码。
what kind of encoding it's using,
what kind of encoding it's accepted.
而且如果是请求的话那就给服务器或者
And based on if it's a request, so
that's something going to the server or
从服务器出来的反应
the response something
coming out of the server,
改变我们要找的头头我们要设定什么样的头
changes what kind of headers we're looking
for, what kind of headers we're gonna set.
我在这里突出了一些常见的标题，
So here I highlighted some
of the common headers,
您可能熟悉的主机标题，
the host header you
probably are familiar with,
它会告诉请求它的去向以及目的地
it tells request where it's going and
what's the destination.
主机很有意思，因为它的一部分是 Nginx 读将请求路由到
Host is really interesting because part of
it is what Nginx reads to route request to
正确的服务器。
their correct server.
还记得我们刚才谈到虚拟主机的方式
Remember earlier how we
spoke about virtual hosts,
如何才能拥有多台服务器?
how I can have multiple servers?
这是 Nginx 如何判断它尝试去的地方是如何解读它的标题。
Part of how Nginx determines where it's
trying to go is reading the header, here.
我觉得头真的很厉害，评得不高吧
And I think headers are really, really
powerful and underrated, we probably don't
想想这些数据是如何形成的以及它的用途。
think that much about how that data is
formed and what it's been used for.
但在这件事中， Nginx 正在阅读， Express 不关心这件事。
But in this case, Nginx is reading it,
Express doesn't care anything about it.
其实我可以把主机取出来，还可以，但是
In fact, I can take out the host header,
and it would still work, but
你会遇到一些问题
you'd run into some issues.
有趣的是，我可以代理请求，记住代理是什么 ?
And funny enough, I can proxy requests,
remember what a proxy is?
我们早该定义的
We defined it earlier.
>> Jem Young: 任何人，告诉我?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Anybody, tell me?
没人记得吗
Nobody remembered?
怎么了
Yes?
>> 演讲者 4: 当您拥有代表多个不同服务器的服务器时
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: It's when you have a server
that represents multiple different
它后面的端点，它根据，重新路由和重定向，
endpoints behind it, and
it reroutes and redirects based on,
在这种情况下，逆向代理。
in this case, the reverse proxy.
>> Jem Young: 完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly, exactly right.
有趣的是，某些标题是由客户端不可修改的，并且
Funny enough, there are certain headers
that are unmodifiable by the client, and
主机头是其中之一。
the host header is one of them.
我不知道我的请求来自哪里，浏览器不允许这样做。
I cannot fake where my request came from,
browsers don't allow that generally.
因此，如果您有服务工作者并且正在尝试使用服务工作者作为代理，
So if you have a service worker and you're
trying to use a service worker as a proxy,
我该回去了
I should step back.
有人知道服务工人是什么吗 ?
Does anybody know what
a service worker is?
你听过这个短语，它是一个持续的 Web 工作者，在一个单独的线程中运行，
You've heard the phrase, it's a persistent
web worker that runs in a separate thread,
当选项卡关闭时，它仍可以在后台运行。
and when the tab is closed,
it can still run in the background.
本质上是拦截网络请求的方法
It's a way of intercepting
network requests, essentially,
它也能做其他事情
it can do other things, too.
还有一个关于 FrontEnd Masters on service 工作者的好课程
And there's a good course on FrontEnd
Masters on service workers taught by
有人我忘了谁
somebody, I forget who.
>> 演讲者 5: 凯尔 - 辛普森。 >> Jem Young: 凯尔 - 辛普森
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: Kyle Simpson.
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Kyle Simpson, yeah, and
他太聪明了
he's brilliant, so take that course.
但是一个服务工作者，我最早尝试做的事情之一就是我试图创造
But a service worker, one of the things I
tried to do early on was I tried to create
在客户机中发出代理，因此
out a proxy in the client, so
根据请求尝试执行的操作来代理不同的服务器。
that based on what the request is trying
to do it proxy the different servers.
我发现你做不到因为我不能修改主机标题
And I found out you couldn't do it because
I can't modify the host header, I can't
修改该包应在请求中运行的位置。
modify where that packet is supposed to
go once the request has gone in flight.
如果您开始使用头进行消息传递，那么您可能在其中运行
Where in fact you might run into if
you start messing with headers and
服务工作者，用户代理程序为下一个。
service workers,
user agent is the next one.
用户代理程序是什么 ?
What does the user agent?
我向你保证如果你的网站开发者以前听过的话
I promise you if your web developer
you've heard the phrase before,
用户代理标题是什么 ?
what's the user agent header?
>> 演讲者 6: 浏览器，信息一般?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: A browser,
information general?
>> Jem Young: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah.
> > 演讲者 7: 是的，你拥有什么样的电脑，那种东西。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: Yeah, what kind of
computer you own, that kind of stuff.
> > Jem Young: 是的，你有没有想过他们为什么会这样 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, do you ever
wonder why they look like this?
这件奇怪的事吗
This weird mishmash of things?
我一直都是，它是早在没有很多的时候，
I always have, it comes from the early
days when there weren't many,
有一个浏览器很受支持，那就是 Internet Explorer，
there was one browser that's well
supported, and that was Internet Explorer,
那就是切割的边缘
and that was the cutting edge.
你有问题吗
Do you have a question?
>> 演讲者 8: 是否进行版本控制?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 8: Is it versioning?
这些数字是数字吗 ?
Is that what the numbers are?
>> Jem Young: 部分是版本控制，但是
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Part of it is versioning,
but
它之所以是这种不同类型的字母汤 [INAUDIBLE] HTML，
the reason why it's this kind of alphabet
soup of different types, [INAUDIBLE] HTML,
我们在很长很长的时间里都没有使用过旧的引擎盖奇
which we haven't used in a long,
long time, like Gecko, the old engine.
因为浏览器是，嘿，我是现代引擎，但我不是
It was because browsers were, hey,
I'm a modern engine, but I'm not
Internet Explorer ，并且仅为 Internet Explorer 构建了大量站点，
Internet Explorer, and a lot of sites
were only built for Internet Explorer,
我们是 Mozilla或 Safari 之类的所以他们伪造了
we're Mozilla, or Safari, or
something like that, so they faked it.
他们把 Mozilla 放到标题里，即使在这个情况下，这是一个 Chrome
They put Mozilla in the header, even
though, in this case, this was a Chrome
但是它还是会说 Mozilla 5.0 因为它是在伪装自己
browser, but it still says Mozilla 5.0
because it's trying to fake itself.
而且因为网络是向后兼容的，所以他们保留了它，
And because the web is backwards
compatible, they kept it, and
它的时间越来越长，没有一家公司说过，哎，
it just keeps getting longer and longer,
and no one company has ever said, hey,
我们今天要解决这个问题我们要解决这个问题
we're gonna fix this today, we're
gonna fix this because now there's so
许多不同的浏览器，没有人同意用户代理的外观。
many different browsers and no one would
agree on what the user agent looks like.
但是，真正的用户代理是我们使用它来检查我们所使用的浏览器版本，
But really the user agent is we use it to
inspect what version of browser we're on,
那么支持的功能部件以及它基本上是什么类型的浏览器。
so what features are supported and
what type of browser it is basically.
通常，您将使用用户代理的某些库部分，因为
Generally, you're gonna use some sort of
library parts of your user agent because
这些都是不可读的，就像我从 Google Chrome 浏览器中提取的。
these are generally unreadable, like I
pulled this from Google Chrome browser.
但就好像很难知道是哪个浏览器
But like it'd be very difficult
to tell which browser it was,
它是 Chrome，是 Safari，是 Mozilla吗 ?
is it Chrome, is it Safari, is it Mozilla?
没人知道，如果你想嗅到用户代理，那么使用库。
No one knows, so use a library if
you're trying to sniff user agents.
但是再次，功能部件支持非常好，因此如果我想打开类似的内容
But again, it's good for a feature
support, so if I wanna turn on like top
级别异步等待 V8 现在支持，但它不支持其他浏览器。
level async await which V8 now supports
but it's not supporting other browsers.
我已使用某种用户代理程序嗅探或其他方法。
I already use some sort of user
agent sniffing or other methods.
接受只是说作为一个浏览器
Accept is just saying, as a browser,
我能从服务器接收到什么东西 ?
what sort of things can I
receive back from the server?
因为并非所有 Web 浏览器都支持所有相同的协议，但是
Because not all web browsers
support all the same protocols, but
接受头通常由浏览器本身生成。
the accept header is usually
generated by the browser itself.
它就会说，嘿，你知道我要用这个文本格式的 HTML ，
And it just says, hey, you know what
I'll take HTML in that text format,
我们用的是不同类型的
and we use that for
different types, we use that for
不同类型的支持格式，我们向下移动到接受编码。
different types of supportive formats,
we move down to the accepting coding.
这就意味着这个浏览器接受这些 gzip 编码，所以 Nginx 会说，嘿，
That just means this browser accepts these
gzip encoding so Nginx will say, hey,
我这里有个请求它会在出去的路上
I've got a request here and
it'll actually take gzips on the way out,
我要加把头因为我知道 Azure 能搞定
I'm gonna gzip that up because
I know Azure can handle that.
虽然不是每个浏览器都支持 gzip，
Whereas back in the day not
every browser support the gzip,
在这种情况下，因为我是使用 Chrome 作为这个用户代理，也可能接受，
in this case, because I'm using Chrome as
this user agent, it also accepts probably,
我们之前说过的是一种替代压缩格式
which we talked about earlier as
a alternative compression format invented,
我想在瑞士说，是，是在瑞士发明的。
I wanna say in Switzerland,
yes, invented in Switzerland.
我怎么会知道
Why do I know that?
库兹我在瑞士，我大概就是，而且实际上是指小面包。
Cuz I was in Switzerland, and I was like
probably, and actually means little bread.
很好你学习各种各样的东西不仅是速速和富激情的
Good, you learn all sorts of things
not just Fast and Furious trivia, but
它是不同的编码格式，但是它只是说，嘿，如果是 Nginx，或者 Apache ，
it's a different encoding format, but it's
just saying, hey, if Nginx, or Apache, or
任何使用，支持的 Web 服务器，我的浏览器也会接受。
whatever web server using, supports
probably, my browser will accept it too.
这真的很棒，对我们来说，它就像回到了不同的事物中。
And it's really nice, cuz it's a way of
like falling back to different things.
再次，所有这些都包含在标题中，
And again,
all this is contained in the header,
就像所有关于请求本身的元数据一样。
like all this metadata
about the request itself.
当然，除了语言，我还想说什么语言呢 ?
And of course, except languages, what sort
of languages am I expecting to get back?
这些内容通常由浏览器自动填充，以及您说过的任何语言
These are generally auto populated by the
browser, and whatever language you've said
在浏览器或您的操作系统 >> Jem Young : And
in the browser or your operating system
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
我只是去接管你的一些普通头头
I'm just going over some of
the common headers you'll run into,
我没说的是 Set-cookies ，它设置了 cookie。
the one I didn't talk about was
Set-cookie which sets cookies.
为什么 cookies 对 Web 很重要 ?
Why are cookies kind of
important to the web?
>> Jem Young: 或者我应该说什么是曲奇 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Or
should I say what is a cookie?
是吗 ?
Yeah?
>> 扬声器 7: 这是一个元数据，但它会在每个后续请求中进行。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: It's a piece of metadata,
but it goes on every subsequent request.
它也可以在服务器端进行检查和管理。
And it can be inspected and
kinda managed on the server side too.
>> Jem Young: 确实，它是持久的文本数据，持久存储在
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly, it's a persistent
bit of text data that persists on
浏览器，取决于它是否是会话 cookie，
the browser,
depending on if it's a session cookie,
意味着在关闭选项卡或浏览器时，将擦除，或
meaning the minute you close a tab or
the browser, it's gonna be erased, or
常规 cookie ，将持续一段时间。
a regular cookie,
which will persist over time.
当您在 cookie 工具上设置到期时，它将到期。
And it will expire whenever you
set the expire on the cookie tool.
但为什么 cookie 很重要?
But why is the cookie important?
事实上这对网络很重要
In fact, it's crucial to the web,
就像我们不能在没有饼干的情况下
like we couldn't we couldn't
operate a web without cookies.
有谁有吗坦纳
Anybody, [INAUDIBLE], Tanner?
>> 演讲者 8: [INAUDIBLE] 让您在会话之间带来数据
&gt;&gt; Speaker 8: [INAUDIBLE] let's you
bring data between sessions and
例如，您可以在不同会话中扩展用户体验。
like let's you extend the user
experience across different sessions.
>> Jem Young: 没错，我们不认为什么是开发者，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly, there's something
we don't think about as what developers,
网络是无状态的，每个请求和响应都是全新的
is that the internet is stateless,
every request and response is a brand new
服务器不记得您在这里的请求和响应。
request and response the server doesn't
remember that you've been here or not.
Versus 表示其他编程范例，其中有一个状态和
Versus say other programming paradigms,
where there's a state and
当用户离开时，该状态就会消失。
then whenever the user goes
away that state is gone.
网络是无国籍的我们不认为它存在
The web is stateless, it's something
we don't think about that it exists,
所以我们需要在一段时间里对这些数据进行对比以便我们知道
so we need cookies versus this data over
time so that we know that a request,
表示此人已登录或已注销，或者我接受 cookie 条幅
say the person is logged in or they're
logged out, or I accept cookie banner
我们现在都得这么做了
that we all have to do now because
of regulations or things like that.
我很高兴你把这个给我带来了
The danger with cookies and
I'm glad you brought that up, Kayla,
除非您将 cookie 到期，否则 cookie 会在每个请求上持久存储。
is that cookies persist over every
single request unless you expire them.
最糟糕的是你能提出一个很简单的要求
And the bad thing about that is you
can make a really simple request,
如我想要 2 千字节 HTML 页面， 10 千字节( 如果
like I want a 2 kilobyte HTML page,
10 kilobytes, if
你在那儿放了很多曲奇因为它们是在每一个请求中发送的
you put a lot of cookies in there, because
they're sent on every single request.
所以如果我想说的是网络开发商和全堆的工程师
So if I to tip is web developers and
full stack engineers,
注意您发送的 cookie 量，并且不要在其中添加太多数据，
be careful the amount of cookies you send,
and don't add too much data in there,
因为它会在每一个请求中被发送出去
because it's gonna get sent
on every single request and
你只是在增加开销而你的连接会变得更慢
you're just adding overhead, and
you're making your connection slower.
我想说的共同标题的最终类型有很多很多
The final type of common header I
wanna talk about, there are lots and
很多头，我只碰其中的几个，是 X 头。
lots of headers, I'm just touching
on a few of them, is the X header.
X 是有关如何设置定制头的一般准则，因此
X is a general guideline on
how to set custom headers, so
如果你想让杰姆成为最好的人
if you're like I wanna set
a Jem is the best header,
我将使用 X 点 Jem 是最佳的标题，并放置您想要的任何类型的数据。
I would use X dot Jem Is the best header
and put whatever sort of data you want.
使用定制头是发送一次性定制数据的良好方法
And using custom headers is a good way
of sending one-time custom data that we
不一定要有有效载荷但我们想用浏览器解密
don't necessarily want a payload but
we wanna be decrypted by the browser.
你可能已经看到了如果你看到 X 的标题
It's something you've probably seen,
if you probably seen X something header,
这就意味着它是一个定制的标题
it just means it's a custom header,
浏览器可能不知道该怎么办
the browser probably doesn't
know what to do with it.
Nginx 可能不知道该怎么做你会最常看到的
The Nginx probably doesn't know what to do
with it, the one you'll see most commonly,
让我们撤下我们的网页，看看我们是否能看到一个定制的标题。
and let's pull up our web page and see
if we can see a custom header in there.
所以我在我的网页上可以自己拉上
So I'm on my web page,
we can pull up your own, and
我要刷新这个页面我要看看 " 网络 " 标签页
I'm gonna refresh this page,
I'm gonna look at the Network tab,
让我们查下请求的信息
and let's check out the request headers.
给定主机，用户代理程序和响应头下的用户代理程序，
Given the host, the user agents, and
we have under the response headers,
我们这个 X 的动力
we this X powered by,
cutz powered by 不是浏览器知道要处理的官方 HP 标题。
cuz powered by is not an official HP
header that browser know to deal with.
快把这个标记给你让你知道
Express just tag this on
to let you know that, hey,
服务的应用程序正在使用 Express。
the application of
a serving is using Express.
因此，如果需要使用 X 发送定制一次性数据
So if you need to send custom
one-time data using an X
标题是执行它的好方法。
header is a good way of doing it.
>> Jem Young: 反应看起来有点不同，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The response
looks a little different, and
头就不一样了
the headers will be a little different.
请求头都是关于我作为浏览器的内容吗 ?
The request header is all about,
who I am as a browser?
我要去哪
Where am I going?
我想去哪
Where am I trying to get to?
我支持什么样的科技激励 ?
What sort of technology
incentives I support?
响应头是服务器发送您的内容，让我们说内容
The response headers is what the server is
sending you so that let's say the content
gzip 编码，浏览器不知道，除非我们设置一个头
is gzip encoded, the browser wouldn't
know that unless we set a header that
内容类型被编码为 gzip，它不知道如何解包。
says the content type is encoded as gzip,
it wouldn't know how to unpack that.
因此，响应头与请求头一样重要。
So the response headers are just as
important as the request headers.